hypeseek.com 2019-02-25

# PRIVACY POLICY | Hype Seek !!

At Hype Seek, our job is to provide you with the best stuff to Entertain you. All images on FullPunch.com are readily available and believed to be in public domain, if you find anything here that violates your copyright you may contact us at john.selby85@gmail.com[  
](http://www.fullpunch.com/privacy-policy/niaz.shomaila@gmail.com)

At [www.hypeseek.com](http://www.fullpunch.com/privacy-policy/www.fullpunch.com), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [www.hypeseek.com](http://www.fullpunch.com/privacy-policy/www.fullpunch.com) and how it is used.

### Third Party Advertising

We use Google AdSense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognise a unique “cookie” on your browser.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

### How To Contact Us

If you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please send us an email at john.selby85@gmail.com.  

Like Hypeseek!! on Facebook, be the first to see our best content!
